{
  "Questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which describes positive pressure breathing?",
      "choices": [
        "A. It is the pulling down of air to the lungs",
        "B. It is the swallowing or the pushing down of air to the lungs",
        "C. It is performed by humans",
        "D. It is the cooling down of air"
      ],
      "answer": "B. It is the swallowing or the pushing down of air to the lungs"
    },
    {
      "question": "Richard and Lucy tried to exhale all the air inside their lungs.  But no matter how hard they exhaled, there were air retained in their lungs.  Which describes this air?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Tidal volume",
        "B. Vital capacity",
        "C. Residual Air",
        "D. Eupnea"
      ],
      "answer": "C. Residual Air"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the opening of the trachea where air enters the insect’s respiratory tract?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Spiracle",
        "B. Bronchiole",
        "C. Tracheole",
        "D. Diaphragm"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Spiracle"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Aorta and the carotid arteries have chemoreceptors that monitor the pH in the blood.",
      "choices": ["A. True", "B. False"],
      "answer": "A. True"
    },
    {
      "question": "The following are considered as organs of the conducting portion of the human’s respiratory tract EXCEPT:",
      "choices": ["A. Nostril", "B. Nasal Cavity", "C. Alveoli", "D. Trachea"],
      "answer": "D. Trachea"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the use of Oxygen that you are inhaling from the environment?",
      "choices": [
        "A. For Photosynthesis",
        "B. For cellular respiration",
        "C. For formation of red blood cells",
        "D. For absorption of nutrients"
      ],
      "answer": "C. For formation of red blood cells"
    },
    {
      "question": "Toads respire through both skin and lungs.",
      "choices": ["A. True", "B. False"],
      "answer": "A. True"
    },
    {
      "question": "When you inspire, you are breathing out air.",
      "choices": ["A. True", "B. False"],
      "answer": "B. False"
    },
    {
      "question": "The functional unit of your lungs is called.",
      "choices": ["A. Alveolus", "B. Nephron", "C. Neuron", "D. Spiracle"],
      "answer": "A. Alveolus"
    },
    {
      "question": "As you inhale, which of the following will NOT occur?",
      "choices": [
        "A. diaphragm contracts",
        "B. diaphragm moves down",
        "C. rib cage moves up",
        "D. lungs expand"
      ],
      "answer": "C. rib cage moves up"
    }
  ]
}
